Contact

Flat 23, The Bayley, 21 New Bailey Street, Manchester, M3 5AX +447907546197 (Mobile) nosy_parker@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jeff-yin-kit-lung-35689666 (LinkedIn) jefflung.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Corporate Identity
Logo Design
Illustration

Languages

Chinese (Native or Bilingual) English (Limited Working)

Certifications

Learn React.js: Part II Course Flavio Copes's JavaScript Fundamentals Certificate in 3D Computer Animation and Modeling

Learn React Course

Jeff(Yin Kit) Lung

Experienced Web Designer

Manchester

Summary

I started working from 2000 when I was a Multimedia Designer in a junior position. Afterwards, I have worked as Graphic Designer and Web Designer. Within my career time, I have used many tools like Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Aftereffect and 3D Software Maya. On the side of web work, I am proficient with Html, CSS and I am enhancing my JavaScript skill and ReactJs now.

Experience

Dreamshub Limited
Web Designer
September 2013 - October 2020 (7 years 2 months)
Hong Kong SAR

InfinMedia Co. LTD.

Multimedia Designer

March 2013 - August 2013 (6 months)

Freelancer
Multimedia Designer
October 2011 - March 2013 (1 year 6 months)

Town Health International Medical Group Graphic Designer July 2009 - September 2011 (2 years 3 months)

Next Dimension Advertising (HK) Limited Multimedia Designer April 2001 - July 2009 (8 years 4 months)

Education

Coventry University

Bachelor of Creative Technologies (BSc. Hon), Creative Technologies · (2011 - 2012)

School for Higher and Professional Education of VTC
Professional Diploma in Game Design & Production, Game Design &
Production · (2010 - 2011)

City University of Hong Kong

Master Class in Charater Animation , Charater Animation · (March
2004 - September 2004)

City University of Hong Kong
Certificate in 3D Computer Animation and Modeling, 3D Computer Animation
and Modeling · (September 2003 - August 2004)

The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology
Diploma in Multimedia Design, Multimedia Design · (May 2002 - April 2003)